

Amina Mahmood

Permanent Address: House # 341 K2 Near Rehmat Chock Wapda Town Lahore

Mobile Number: 0333-4718789■ Phone Number: 0423-5224705

E-mail: aminamahmood35@gmail.com



Personal Profile

Father Name: Mahmood Ahmad Husband Name: Umair Aslam

NIC: 35202-7037234-0 DOB: 04-May-1988 Marital Status: Married

Religion: Islam

Attributes

- -Strong team working
- -Leadership
- -Good Communication skills
- -Positive nature
- -Hardworking
- -Confident
- -Sincere
- -Patience
- -Strong Determination
- -Dynamic and Carrier oriented personality.
- Always ready to adapt and to work in new and changing work environment

Projects

-Characterization of a Poisson Family of Distribution

(Aug 2017 - May 2018) -LCWU, Lahore.

Tools: Latex, R Language

- Thesis on Why Students Move to Abroad for Higher Studies

(Dec, 2009– Sep, 2010)

-PU. Lahore.

Summary

A MS degree holder in the field of Statistics and a double-degree graduate with experience in the field of teaching.

Acquired relevant professional education and training to get the right concepts of teaching. Adept at managing multiple tasks simultaneously such as planning, setting, evaluating exams and assignments as well as actively taking part in staff meetings and Institute programs.

Professional Profile

Experiences

The Global Institute Lahore Oct 2016 - Aug 2017

Responsibilities:

- To teach
- Introduction to Statistical Theory, Business Statistics and

Mathematics

Nafees Model High School Jan 2010-Jan 2012

Responsibilities:

- To teach
 - Mathematics, Computer and Science

Academic Qualification

MS Statistics

3.06 CGPA 2018

Lahore College for Women University, Lahore

B. Ed

67% 2014

Punjab University, Lahore

M. Sc Statistics,

3.49 CGPA 2010

Punjab University, Lahore

B. Sc (Statistics, Mathematics & Economics)

59.9% 2008



Tools: SPSS, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word

Certifications

- -Graphic Design course
- -Virtual University (Apr 2019-Jun 2019)
- -Freelancing course
- -Virtual University (Apr 2019-Jun 2019)
- -Workshop on LaTex: Introduction & Practice LCWU, Lahore 2018
- -1st International Conference on Social Sciences and Humanities in the Millennium Challenges and Prospects
- -Virtual University 2017
- -Training workshop on Data Analysis

-National University of Modern Languages 2017

Languages

English/Urdu

University of the Punjab, Lahore

FA (Statistics, Mathematics & Economics)

70% 2006

Govt Jinnah Degree College for women

Matric

74% 2004

Govt Model Girls High School, Lahore

References:

References can be furnished upon request.